Orphia imagined herself speaking so casually to Rio and laughed shyly.

“Let’s get cooking.”

“Right.” Orphia nodded earnestly.

Then, Rio went back to the backpack and took out two thin metal sheets. Each sheet had a spell formula design on its surface. He placed them on the work table Celia had made and put the pot on top of one of them.

After placing several enchanted gems around the sheet, the spell formula absorbed the essence from the gems and started to release light and heat. This metal sheet was a magic artifact that could be used to control heat in place of a stove. Once a frying pan and some ingredients were also removed from the backpack, they were ready to start their food preparation.

First, vegetable oil and spices were added into the pan with some vegetables and mushrooms they harvested while they walked. Once the mushrooms were soft, slices of dried meat were added. After the flavor of the dried meat seeped into the mushrooms, the heat would be turned off and the contents served onto a plate. Half of this was then given to Orphia to make into soup.

Rio took the now-empty frying pan and added butter and diced onions, heating it until it was soft before adding the barley to fry it.

“Amazing. It’s evident you’re very skilled at this. What is it that you’re making?” Christina asked in awe, having watched them as they went about their preparations.

“This is a type of food called porridge.”

“Porridge, you say?” Christina cocked her head at Rio’s answer.

“It isn’t a type of food that nobility would come across, so I’m not surprised you haven’t heard of it before. You fry the barley in oil before adding water to boil it.”

“It smells good. I can’t wait to try it.” Christina’s nose twitched as she sniffed the air before smiling.

After that, once the barley had been heated to a suitable degree, a small amount of alcohol was added to further fry it. All that was left was to add the solid pseudo-bouillon that had been preserved in a container while making the stew at the inn last night, then boil the water in the pot and melt the bouillon for the flavor to seep in.

...It feels like she’s standing oddly close.

Rio felt a little uncomfortable from Christina’s gaze, who was standing at a distance neither too close nor too far to watch them. Every now and then she looked like she wanted to say something, but she didn’t ask anything other than what they were making.

It doesn’t seem like she’s observing me, though.

If anything, it seemed like a rather hesitant gaze, as though she was gauging his expressions.

Is it because she’s realized my identity after all? But if so, wouldn’t she normally act more guarded...?

Rio recalled the standoffish image Christina had in his academy days.

She seems to have changed a lot—she’s much softer now than she was back then.

Back then, she always seemed to be irritated and consistently distanced herself from others. So much so, they never exchanged a single conversation while he had been there. Perhaps that was why...

It feels kind of strange having her so close by.

It wasn’t a bad thing, but it felt strange after having such a strong image of her past self. Just why was she standing so close and watching him so curiously?

Rio tried to think about it, but he didn’t understand. Since thinking any further wouldn’t help answer his question, he decided to focus silently on making the food before him instead.

The barley had absorbed the moisture well, so the heat was turned off before the contents of the frying pan began to scorch. Then, the mushroom and dried meat was added back into the pan and mixed well with salt and pepper for seasoning, before shredded cheese was finally added.

“It’s done.” The barley cheese risotto was completed.

“I’m done as well.” Orphia finished the soup at just that moment. An appetizing smell wafted from the pot. Cheese risotto with mushroom and wild vegetable soup. It would normally be considered a treat to eat such a thing while camping outdoors.

Furthermore, while Rio had been cooking, Celia had prepared a wonderful dining space. There was a dining table and enough seats for everyone.

Everyone started gathering, drawn by the delicious scent.

“Whoa, isn’t this risotto?! What grain did you use for it?!” Kouta asked, excitement in his eyes.

“It’s barley.”

“Barley, hmm? So that’s how...”

“There’s a thing called barley and rice, after all.”

At Rio’s answer, Kouta and Rei’s eyes widened. They were just like the others that had come from Japan and missed rice too. For the record, Kouta’s barley had been in the language of that world, but Rei’s barley and rice had been in Japanese—mugimeshi.

“Mugimeshi?” Christina finally spoke up. She was cocking her head at the unfamiliar word.

“It’s a type of grain. The main grain that’s eaten in Kouta’s world is called rice, and it’s very similar in shape to barley. The taste and texture is different to barley, but similar dishes can be prepared,” Rio explained to Christina about barley and rice.

“You’re very knowledgeable... Ah, I see. You must have heard it from that Miharu person,” Kouta said.

“Yes. Though limited, there are parts of Strahl where rice is cultivated. I don’t have any on hand right now, but I’d be happy to treat you if there’s an opportunity in the future.”

“R-Really?!” Kouta jumped up eagerly.

“Yes. But for now, you’ll have to make do with barley risotto. Let’s dig in while it’s still hot,” Rio agreed with a smile, then urged them all to begin eating.

“Right, right. This is a treat! It looks really delicious, I can’t wait!”

“Yup, it smells really nice.”

Kouta and Rei both said excitedly.

“Y-Yum!”

“Whoa. The cheese is so thick.”

Kouta and Rei—who knew what a risotto was—praised the food first. After giving their opinions on the first bite, they spent the rest of the time absorbed in eating.

Christina also carried the spoon to her mouth elegantly before blinking in surprise. “Even though the cheese is so rich in taste, it doesn’t feel heavy at all. Impressive,” she offered.

“In order to remove the unique scent barley produces when water is added, the barley is first fried with alcohol. After it’s fried, the recommended order is to soak the barley in soup before finally adding the cheese. That way, the taste of the cheese is condensed,” Rio explained.

“So you first remove the unnecessary flavors from the ingredients, then add the flavors that you want. I see... There’s a lot of thought behind it. And the result is truly delicious...”

Christina hummed in awe before taking another bite of the risotto to savor the taste. Her mouth softened faintly in a bitter and fleeting way.

Chapter 4: Before the Border

Three days had passed since the adventurers at the post town picked a fight with Rio and the others. They had proceeded even further east and were finally approaching the border of Galarc.

Before noon, the group had arrived at a walled city that functioned as a line of defense near the kingdom’s border. However, before everyone entered the city, Rio went alone to check on the state of things. Celia and the rest of the group hid themselves in the forest off the road to the west gate of the city and waited for Rio’s return. They prepared a slightly early lunch and started eating, when Rio silently appeared near them, calling out to them first so as not to scare them.

“Sorry for the wait.”

For the record, Sara and Alma’s contract spirits Hel and Ifrita were watching the area on the ground in their spirit forms, and Orphia’s contract spirit Ariel was on alert in material form in the air, so they would have noticed Rio’s approach. Ariel was the only one in material form because being in material form provided far greater physical abilities, such as the ability to see greater distances, increasing their search capabilities.

Celia ran up to Rio once she spotted him. “Welcome back, Haruto. How was it?”

“There was no wanted notice on the bulletin board of this city, either. I didn’t see any search party personnel performing any searches, but it is a walled city. There are quite a few soldiers on patrol,” Rio reported.

Incidentally, they had passed through numerous cities and towns on their way to this walled city, but none of them had had the same notice.

“If a walled city on the border doesn’t even have the wanted notice, then there’s no doubt that the notice from the post town was completely fabricated,” Christina declared, sighing. It was good to get more accurate information, but said information wasn’t exactly pleasant to hear.

“In other words, Reiss predicted that we would pass through that post town. He should have received information about us turning back west through the adventurers we let go, but who knows how much that can fool him...” Rio furrowed his brows solemnly.

“However, if we look at it from another angle, that means our actual enemy is Reiss alone. That much is certain after the lack of search parties in the places we’ve stopped at up until this point.” Vanessa gave a positive analysis contrary to the pessimistic Christina and Rio. However, Christina reacted to that with a solemn look to match Rio’s.

“Perhaps that may be true for Charles, but...”

The problem was Reiss. Since the incident at the post town, things had gone smoothly—too smoothly. It made Christina feel uneasy about whether they could really make it to Rodania safely.

Rio also had a bad feeling about how well things were going.

“...For now, our shortest goal is to cross the kingdom border before us. We’ll head for the border through the shortest route so that we don’t have to worry about the search party anymore. If we depart now, we should be able to cross the border within the day easily,” he suggested to everyone. Once they passed the walled city before them, there were no more post towns or walled cities until the border.

There was only a short distance left.

No matter what happens, we’ll move forward. Whatever Reiss has planned doesn’t change what we need to do, Rio thought to refocus his mind.

◇　◇　◇

After their discussion, Rio and the others headed for the walled city. Ever since the incident at the post town, they were wary of the possibility that Charles and the pursuit party knew how many of them there were. They usually split up into groups of two before going through the gates of the towns and cities they stopped at, but this time they chose to enter the city as a group of nine.

If they could pass through the gate like this without a problem, that would mean they had conclusive proof that the pursuit party led by Charles was still unaware that Christina was running with a group of nine people.

“We made it,” Celia said in relief once they entered the city without incident.

“Well, that’s only natural. Charles probably thinks we’ve only traveled half as far as we actually have. The fact the gatekeepers are still checking hair colors makes me think we’ve outsmarted them completely,” Vanessa said, looking around at the city. The inside of the walls wasn’t strictly guarded, bustling with people in what seemed to be the picture of serenity.

Rio walked at the head of the party with Celia close beside him, followed by Christina and Vanessa, then Kouta and Rei, and finally Sara, Orphia, and Alma in a long line as they proceeded from the west of the main street to the east. Out of caution for the presence of the pursuit party, Christina, Vanessa, Kouta, and Rei covered their faces with hoods. Everyone else had their hoods down as they walked.

Celia and the spirit folk girls’ appearances did draw attention, but there were many pedestrians, so the most people could manage was a double or triple take. There were some people who bumped into others and couples that bickered briefly about it, but it was mostly uneventful.

Thus, they walked straight down the main street from the west gate to the east gate and stepped out onto the road.

After leaving the east gate, Rio stared down the road to the border and turned to the party. “All right, let’s go. We should cross the border in about an hour’s time on foot. Our formation will be the same as usual: I’ll take the lead and Sara’s group will surround Her Highness and Celia.”

Rio, Sara, Orphia and Alma formed a diamond formation and walked with caution directed in every direction.

The weather was clear, so there were others leaving the east gate to head for the kingdom border just like them. Their view of their surroundings was clear, but in ten minutes’ time, the city behind them could no longer be seen.

There’s surprisingly few people heading from Galarc to Beltrum. Well, with the kingdom being in the state it is, I doubt many would come here voluntarily... Rio thought to himself. When he looked around them, all he could see were the adventurers that had left the walled city at practically the same time as them.

Suddenly, four adventurers appeared in front of them, walking from the opposite direction. Three were armed with swords, and the fourth was a slender man whose face was covered by a hood.

“Everyone, please keep to the left,” Rio directed the party. It was polite to stick to one side of the road so that others could pass along the other side in cases like this; it was a worldly wisdom that prevented a lot of trouble when people were traveling.

However, the slender, hooded man purposefully cut in front of them and stopped them from moving any further.

“...Please halt,” Rio ordered the party without turning to look. Celia and the others behind him came to a complete stop. Meanwhile, the three remaining men on the other side started surrounding their group.

“Why, what a coincidence this is,” the hooded man said. His voice was familiar.

“Reiss, huh?” Rio immediately drew the sword at his waist and glared at Reiss. Sara and the others behind him had also drawn their weapons, pointing them at the three male adventurers who similarly had their swords drawn.

“Oh? You’re less surprised than I expected,” Reiss said, wide-eyed.

“We knew from that wanted notice that you were trying to locate us. We tried to camouflage our route, but we were prepared to be attacked at any moment.”

“Haha, I see. You really are a terrifying person.”

“You don’t look like you actually think that in the slightest.”

“That’s not true. I find you scary.”

“...You showed yourself rather boldly, if that was true. Is your aim Princess Christina’s life?” Rio asked flatly with a cold glare.

“Hehe.” A fearless smile tugged at Reiss’ mouth.

“There’s something I want to ask you before I defeat you here.”

There was no point in asking anything else. Rio braced his sword.

“Is it about our captain, Lucius? Or is it about your past... Oh my, that’s dangerous.” Reiss chuckled with scorn. However, Rio slashed at him mid-sentence, making him take a large leap backwards.

“There’s no telling what you’re scheming, after all. I’ll listen to what you have to say after I beat you.” Rio glared at Reiss sharply.

“Now, don’t be like that. I’ve even gone and brought out members of the Heavenly Lions for you today. They’re the subordinates of that man you’re so familiar with, and they’re all quite skilled. I’m sure they’ll be a good match for your girls,” Reiss said casually, looking at Arein, Lucci, and Ven who were all glaring at Sara and the others.

“That’s right. Play with us a little, ladies,” Lucci said to Alma, whom he was facing.

“Don’t play around. Act seriously,” Ven said, facing Orphia.

“So, you’re my opponent. You sure seem strong.” Arein laughed boldly as he taunted Sara.

“...”

The girls didn’t respond to their taunts, and instead silently watched for their opponent’s first moves. The two sides were roughly five meters apart. They knew that whoever stepped forward first would mark the immediate start of the battle.

Training and ability aside, Sara and the girls are overwhelmingly lacking in combat experience against people who have intentions to kill. Their opponents are humans that will kill without hesitation. We also have to protect Professor Celia and Princess Christina on our side. Depending on their abilities, we may be forced into a tough fight.

In this situation, Rio couldn’t wander too far from Celia or Christina. He put several meters distance between himself and Reiss, thinking about Sara and the others behind him.

“Four capable fighters glaring at each other. Well, a situation like this would inevitably end in a stalemate. However, what if we had more allies on our side?” Reiss said with a grin.

What...? Rio furrowed his brows dubiously. The only ones there were Rio, Reiss, and their respective parties. Other than that—

Don’t tell me...

The adventurers who had left the walled city at the same time as them were still there. They had been watching when Rio and the others were suddenly caught in a tense situation on the road, but Rio anticipated that these men were the allies Reiss just mentioned. There were roughly ten of them.

“All right! Everyone, charge!” Lucci yelled.

“Augendae Corporis! Raaaah!” The men on the road all chanted a spell at once, drawing their swords and began charging toward the formation Rio’s party had set up.

“Wha?!” The party was taken aback. Among them, the first one to react was Rio.

“What?!” He cut in front of the adventurers closest to him, swinging his sword to create a huge gale to blow the men away.

“Sara, Orphia, Alma! Take Celia and Her Highness through the gaps in their formation and go on ahead! I’ll handle this!” he ordered.

“But...” Sara and the others hesitated.

“Like I’d let you!” Lucci yelled as he slashed at Rio.

“Silence.” Rio flicked his sword horizontally towards Lucci. The two of them clashed, sword against sword.

“W-Whoa... Oh, damn!” Lucci’s body was easily blown ten meters away. If he hadn’t been holding an enchanted sword and had his body enhanced with sorcery, the force would have cut his sword and torso in half.

“Is this guy for real? Just what kind of body enhancement sorcery is he using?” Lucci gave a stiff smile as he shook it off. The charging adventurers who witnessed the blow came to an abrupt halt.

“Hey! What are you slacking off for?! You’ll be killed!” Arein yelled suddenly. While they were standing around, Rio had already moved on to target the next adventurer, sending several men flying away with another blast of wind.

“Quickly, everyone!” Rio ordered Sara.

“E-Everyone, this way! Alma, Orphia, you two take the rear!” Sara snapped to her senses and started rushing through the gaps Rio made in the enemy circle. Celia and the others followed her.

“Lucci, Ven! Don’t let your guard down. This is the guy that got the better of our leader. You’ll die if you’re not careful! Use everything you’ve got! Augendae Corporis!” Arein yelled, chanting a spell before charging at Rio. A physical body enhancement via spirit arts and a physical ability enchantment through magic or sorcery. Normally, it was impossible for the latter to surpass the former in terms of physical abilities, but—

“Uh...” Rio briefly gazed in wonder. Arein’s speed had been dramatically increased with Augendae Corporis. In fact, it was a speed on par with a body strengthening spirit art that would’ve used up a fair amount of magic essence.

It’s not just a normal Augendae Corporis? Rio thought, receiving Arein’s attack.

“Blocking that with such a composed look...” Arein’s expression was strained.

“Augendae Corporis!” Lucci and Ven both chanted. A geometric-patterned magic circle appeared, wrapping around their bodies.

“I hate how this makes my whole body ache!”

“It’s better than dying!”

Lucci and Ven both charged at Rio from different directions.

Their speeds were equivalent to Arein. Lucci must have also enhanced his physical body with his enchanted sword earlier, as his current speed was significantly faster.

“The three of us will hold this guy back! All of you, catch the ones that got away!” Lucci ordered the remaining adventurers. They began pursuing Sara and the others.

So they’ve enhanced their physical abilities with magic on top of strengthening their bodies with their enchanted swords...

Rio found it to be reckless. It was a so-called double enchantment—sure, doing so would allow them to surpass the physical ability boost that the enchanted sword allowed them, but it would place a huge burden on their bodies.

However, the effect was remarkable, as it allowed Arein, Lucci, and Ven to press Rio back when they teamed up.

“Master Reiss, we can’t last long over here!” Arein yelled. Rio used the faint moment of distraction from Arein and the others to slip past them, rushing over to the adventurers pursuing Celia’s group in an instant. However—

“I won’t let you do that.” Reiss moved at an equally impressive speed, firing several high-speed balls of light towards Rio, who was closing in on the adventurers.

“Guh...” Rio swung his sword, erasing the ball of light. However, Reiss’ attack didn’t end there. Without even chanting a spell, he continued to freely create balls of light and fire them towards Rio. The orbs rained down like a storm, but Rio weaved between them in a zigzag trajectory to magnificently evade them all.

“Goodness me, what a tremendous reaction speed,” Reiss muttered in awe. Then, Arein, Lucci, and Ven appeared.

“My apologies, Master Reiss,” Arein apologized.

“This won’t do. You have to hold him here properly,” Reiss said in exasperation.

“The bastard started moving at a ridiculous speed,” said Lucci.

“He’s manipulating the wind to accelerate. From what I can see, it appears to be an application of flying spirit arts, but it is quite the reckless approach. The slightest mistake could send you hurtling into an obstacle for quite a lot of damage, so you’d need a powerful body enhancement going at the same time—it’s not a technique I’d consider possible for a human to use. Let’s see, if I were to try it...”

Reiss trailed off and disappeared instantly. The next moment—

“Wha?!”

Rio also disappeared.

The destination of the two who had disappeared was where Celia and the others were currently fleeing. They were over 50 meters away, but they traveled that distance in an instant.

Rio barely managed to get in front of Reiss and wedged himself before the group. Once he did, Reiss came to a sudden stop as well.

“W-When did he...”

They had been running with their physical abilities enchanted by magic. Yet, Rio and Reiss had suddenly appeared from behind them, which came as a shock to Kouta and Rei. Christina and Vanessa also stared, wide-eyed.

“Ah, it seems like I’m no match in terms of speed, as expected. That aside, are you really human?” Reiss ignored the shock of Christina and the others as he looked at Rio with a cool expression.

“What does that make you, then?” Rio asked back plainly.

“Haha.” Reiss laughed eerily. Arein, Lucci, and Ven all caught up once again.

“Wouldn’t it have been better for you to take on this bastard from the start, Master Reiss?” Arein asked tiredly.

“In all probability, I would have lost. But, well, I suppose that isn’t a bad idea,” Reiss boasted in an arrogant tone.

“...” Rio remained silent as he stared at Reiss with a sharp gaze.

“My, my. I thought I had grabbed you by surprise with my movement technique just now, but it seems we’re back at square one. What a terrifying person indeed.” Reiss shook his head in disappointment.

“Orphia, please take Celia and the others and go on ahead. Alma and I will remain here to support Haruto,” Sara ordered as she stood alongside Rio. She held a dagger in each hand and was braced for battle.

“Got it.” With a nod, Alma held her mace in her hand at the ready and stood beside Rio, too.

“Sara...” Rio frowned apologetically.

“Reiss’ power seems to be equal to the higher-ranked warriors of our village. And those three men over there can put up a fair fight against Haruto. It only makes sense for us to remain here, in case all four of them try to attack at the same time,” Sara said firmly.

“...Thank you. Could the two of you lend me your strength, then? I’ll take on Reiss,” Rio said gratefully to them, lifting his sword.

“Of course. Alma and I will handle the rest,” Sara said. Arein and the others furrowed their brows at being lumped together with the group of adventurers.

“Orphia, I entrust Celia and Her Highness to you. Cross the border if you can.”

“Yes, leave it to me! Let’s go, everyone!” Orphia said, urging Celia and Christina and the others to depart again. Celia turned back for a brief moment.

“Haruto, Sara, Alma! Win!” she said.

“Of course.”

“Yes!”

The three shouted back. At that, Celia turned and ran after Orphia, with Kouta and Rei in tow. Christina stopped to say something to them, but—

“Princess Christina, hurry!” Vanessa urged.

“...Right.” Christina began running with a somewhat pained expression.

“Good grief,” Reiss said, smiling for some reason. “Arein, Lucci, Ven, and everyone else. Please entertain those ladies over there. It’s irritating, but I shall take on the boy,” he said.

“Right. Now that we’ve been treated as the accessories, our reputation is on the line,” Arein said with a hostile expression.

“Let’s teach them some manners,” Lucci agreed.

“I’m relying on you, then,” Reiss said, before suddenly disappearing once again. Immediately afterwards—

Above.

Rio followed Reiss’s movements and leaped up into the sky. One beat later, a violent exchange of blows began in the air, rumbling with a tremendous sound.

“Wow, he’s one outrageous monster. I can see why the captain was seriously wounded.” Lucci looked up at the sky in exasperation.

“I’ve always thought we hadn’t seen Master Reiss’ true potential, but to think it was this much...” Ven muttered in reverence.

“Don’t tell me you two are on par with that monster, too.” Arein looked at Sara and Alma.

“Rest assured, the two of us are weaker than Rio,” Sara noted.

“Indeed,” Alma agreed.

“However, we’re not weak enough to lose to you,” Sara added, provoking Arein and his group.

“Hmm...”

“Let’s see, then...”

Without any signal at all, Arein and Lucci leaped at Sara and Alma simultaneously. They closed the distance in one bound and slashed at the two of them.

“Hah!” Sara used her two daggers while Alma used her mace to parry the attacks.

“Ha, so you CAN put up a fight!” Lucci smiled with hostility.

“Do you have the leisure to be smiling?” Alma asked plainly, putting her weight into her mace.

The clash of their weapons sent Lucci flying. He soared several meters through the air and landed on the ground, wincing as he yelled. “W-What?! Whoa there... H-Hey hey, this tiny brat has just as much brute strength as that bastard!”

Elder dwarves were born with musculature that differed from humans. Even the petite and dainty Alma had enough hidden strength to far surpass the large-framed Lucci.

“How savage.” Alma gripped her mace and went to pursue Lucci, but—

“I won’t let you! Ngh!” Ven intervened to stop Alma’s advance. However, after seeing the brute strength that she displayed with Lucci earlier, he decided to parry the heavy blow by leaping backwards. Even then, he grimaced at the burden placed on his arms.

“You don’t seem to have as much power as that tiny one,” Arein analyzed while exchanging blows with Sara.

“That’s right. My strength is in my speed, so.” Sara nodded without showing any vexation and stepped back. Then, she stepped to the right.

“Hah, I can see you clearly, though! ...What?!”

Arein responded to Sara’s movements and tried to cut around her with a smug smile. But before he knew it, Sara had stepped to the left, luring Arein’s body into reflexively heading left. Using that brief opening, Sara stepped right once again and slashed at Arein.

“Wha... N-No! He did it!” Charles flinched, pointing at Alfred as he backed away.

“You ordered it.”

Rio continued to approach, then held his sword ready and swung it.

“Eek...!” Overwhelmed, Charles was unable to move. However, Alfred stepped in front of him and stopped the blow of Rio’s sword.

“Charles, retreat if you do not want to die,” Alfred said with a stern expression.

“W-What?! You dare order your commander...?!”

“Hurry! Did you not witness how fast he got here?!”

Even at a time like this, Charles snapped back reflexively, but Alfred shot down his objection forcibly.

“Guh...!” Rio swung his sword fully and sent Alfred’s body flying back, colliding with Charles along the way.

“H-How dare you! K-Kill him! Someone! Anyone! Hurry and kill that man!” Charles rolled along the ground and remained there as he wailed his orders. The griffin knights in the air immediately moved in response, but Rio thrust his sword upwards. Just as he did, a tornado-like blast of wind burst forth. In a single strike of his sword, he sent all the knights in the sky scattering.

“Wha...” Charles was wide-eyed and speechless.

“Do you understand, now? Numbers and tactics will no longer decide the outcome of this fight,” Alfred said to Charles as he faced Rio.

“Then you do something about him! Use that sword of yours! Flash Judgment, wasn’t it?”

“I would have done so already if I could... I’ll buy you time. Take the soldiers and retreat.”

“...Guh!” Charles whipped around and started running towards the soldiers on the hill.

“Haruto!” Sara and Alma had finally caught up and were calling Rio’s name from behind him.

“Can I leave this to you? I need to capture the enemy’s commander.” Rio fixed his eyes on Alfred, who stood in the way of the fleeing Charles.

“Yes!” came the reply from behind, and Rio rushed forward, but was intercepted by Alfred.

Alfred’s sword immediately began glowing, then shot out light to mow down the area as he slashed with it. However, Rio released a tornado-like blast of wind to offset Alfred’s strike. Alfred continued firing slashes of light one after another. Rio did the same with his wind. It was an exchange of light and wind from the two warriors.

The slashes of light consumed a lot of magic essence, so it wasn’t something that one normally used recklessly—but this was Alfred’s last resort after he sensed the gap in their abilities with his first attack. If he faced Rio with only his sword, he would lose.

However, there was no change to the fact Rio’s physical abilities far surpassed his. Alfred was gradually being pushed back towards the hill.

“Ugh...”

At some point, Rui had made his way around to the hill where Charles had fled. He fired a lightning arrow towards Rio.

Rio took a step back and cut down the arrow, then paused and looked at Rui. “...Are you going to get in my way?”

“Long time no see, Haruto—I haven’t seen you since the Galarc royal castle, I believe?” Rui greeted Rio.

“Indeed,” Rio replied shortly.

“I didn’t want to see you again like this, if possible...” Rui admitted a little awkwardly.

“Neither did I. If you don’t get in my way, I won’t need to attack you.”

Rui gave a pained smile and shook his head slowly. “Unfortunately, I cannot allow that. I’m the hero of their kingdom, after all.”

“...Then I shall do my best not to kill you,” Rio said with a sigh, his aggression waning.

“Haha. I don’t want to kill you either, but I don’t think I can stop you with weak attacks.”

“The attacks you’ve fired until now haven’t been a problem.”

“Is that so? Then...”

Rio and Rui both readied their weapons. Alfred also adjusted his grip on his sword, ready to face Rio once again.

Rio closed in on Alfred, but Rui’s lightning arrow interrupted him. His aim was truly precise—it wouldn’t have been fatal if it had made contact, but it was able to limit Rio’s movements for a brief moment. Alfred wouldn’t let that moment go to waste.

Now that it had come to this, Rio had to change his fighting style as well, as it was difficult to force his way through with his strength alone.

“Hah!”

He decided to overwhelm them with speed. Accelerating his body with wind spirit arts, he closed in on Alfred.

Rio’s method of moving so quickly involved a combination of martial arts that minimized his own movements and wind spirit arts—it was a technique of Rio’s own making. The greatest merit to using it was that the excess movements of the body were practically nonexistent, which made one faster. Thanks to that, it was possible to move in a way that was almost like teleportation.

“Guh...” His many long years of experience allowed Alfred to see through the faint, faint omen of an attack and respond instantaneously. But even as he stopped the attack, he was pushed backwards.

So he was able to react to that just now...

Rio stopped, his eyes widening faintly. Without the intent to kill, he had suppressed his acceleration a little, but even then he had charged with a considerable amount of speed. It was a speed that even elite warriors like the spirit folk village’s head warrior Uzuma or veteran warrior Gouki would have trouble reacting to.

In other words, Alfred was in a league of his own.

“So fast!”

Rio sensed another attack from Rui and sped up again. He disappeared in an instant, surprising Rui, who had just fired another lightning arrow. But even then, the physical body enhancement from his Divine Arms adapted accordingly, firing an arrow of lightning at Rio as he moved. However, Rio moved too fast for the attacks to hit. He would disappear from his position the moment the shots were fired; he was moving too fast for Rui to fire predictively as well.

When he’s this close, his speed makes it hard for me to do anything. Guh...

Rui distanced himself from Rio a little to gain an advantage, then tried to snipe him. But Rio predicted that and drew closer to Rui to knock him out first.

“Haaah!” However, Alfred charged at Rio to protect Rui. He still had some fight left in him after all.

Rio raised his sword to engage Alfred, whose sword started glowing once again. Rio also poured magic essence into his sword to cover it with wind. Then, the two of them swung at each other, creating a tremendous shockwave. The recoil nearly knocked them backwards, but Rio remained standing where he was through the use of his ultra-enhanced physical abilities. Then, he went chasing after Alfred—who had been blown backwards—and swung his sword vertically upwards.

“Guh...” Alfred was able to counter the sudden attack with his sword, but the tremendous physical strength and wind pushed him back, instantly sending him flying upwards into the air.

Rui had aimed for the timing that Rio swung his sword upwards to fire his sniping shot, but his arrow was unable to find its target. No sooner had Rio swung his sword had he chased Alfred into the skies with a giant leap, using the wind from his sword to propel himself and accelerate.

“What the...” Alfred watched Rio flying towards him from the ground in amazement.

Does he plan on finishing this in the air? Then I have no choice.

Alfred sensed that this was to be the final blow and poured the entirety of his remaining magic essence into his enchanted sword. The more essence this sword absorbed, the more powerful of a strike it could release. Thus, Alfred’s sword began glowing the brightest it had yet.

Rio’s expression was stern as Alfred’s eyes focused solely on him.

In that case, I’ll force him into submission. He had planned on ending things in the next attack anyway.

Meanwhile Rio also poured an extraordinary amount of essence into his sword, compressing the energy into a tremendous blast of wind. The two of them gripped their swords and took aim, then released the essence in their swords. A stream of light rushed out of Alfred’s sword, while Rio’s sword released a violent tornado. Their attacks collided.

“Aah!”

Light illuminated the entire area as the windstorm caused a huge explosion. Christina and the others on the ground were nearly blown away.

“S-Sir Amakawa defeated Alfred...” Christina witnessed the sight of Rio holding his sword in the air and a limp, unconscious Alfred. Rio was looking down at the hill, his sword tightly in his grasp. At the end of his line of sight was Charles, who had fled into the army on the hill.

“Huh?!” Charles noticed Rio was staring straight at him from above and flinched.

“Now!” From the ground below, Rui took aim at Rio and fired a thick arrow of lightning—which was really more like a cannon than an arrow. However, Rio was able to move freely in mid-air and evaded the attack. He moved over to where Alfred was passed out and grabbed him.

“Ngh...” Unable to shoot with Alfred in the way, Rui lowered his bow. Rio descended slowly and lowered Alfred to the ground.

“...Huh?” Everyone present on the battlefield watched on as he yet again disappeared without a trace. Rui had a bad feeling and lifted his bow, when suddenly, Rio was standing right before his eyes.

“Tch...”

It was already too late. A palm was thrust into his abdomen and he fell to his knees.

“It’s over,” Rio said.

“Indeed. You really are an amazing person... But, it may have been better to lose here.” Rui chuckled after muttering that, then let himself fall unconscious. With that, there was no one left on this battlefield that could face Rio.

“...” Rio peered at the thousands beyond the hill and slowly began walking.

“A-All of you! Stop him!” Charles yelled frantically, seeing Rio approaching from afar. But the soldiers’ movements lagged, and no one tried to obstruct Rio’s way. In fact, as Rio eventually reached the hill, the soldiers parted like a wave to allow him to pass.

“H-Hey!” Charles looked around at the soldiers, seeking salvation, but reality was cruel indeed.

“Eek!” Charles cowered at the sight of Rio drawing near. He didn’t even think to run away, understanding that attempting to do so would be futile, whether he liked it or not.

“Marching here so brazenly was your mistake,” Rio said once he reached Charles.

“W-What... What are you...?” Charles fell backwards onto his rear, forgetting all his anger.

“Just a regular human.”

“H-Human? You, a human? Hahaha. Bwahahaha...” Rio’s answer made Charles break down with laughter.

“Come with me.” Rio grabbed Charles by the scruff of his neck and forcibly started dragging him back towards Christina and the others.

Unsurprisingly, there was no one who could stop Rio.